Before we start,
I'd like to have
a preliminary PowWow,
or prelimi-wow,
about what I'm calling
our library's
back door conundrum.
Sounds like a porno
with Kate Winslet.
Abed, ew.
The door on that side
is locked after 5,
which means that most of us have
to walk all the way around.
Now, if we were to move
our meetings to 4:30...
- No.
I have a...
regular class
at that time.
It's like math,
or other regular classes.
Yeah, I have something unimportant
that can't ever move.
Well, maybe one of us
could stand by the back door
and let the rest in?
Mm. I nominate Pierce.
Where is he? I have not seen
him around all day.
I haven't, either.
Well, has anyone called him?
I did.
Several times, actually.
But he never returned my calls.
Oh, no.
Oh, the last thing
I said to him was, "Suck it."
Me too.
Good morning.
Yes.
Oh, thank God.
Whew.
You thought I was dead,
didn't you?
[Group] - No....
[Abed] - I did.
Do you people have any idea
how emasculating that is?
I'm not Mickey Rooney.
You don't have to cross
your fingers
to see if I'll show up.
You know, when I was 30,
people used to wish that
I was dead to my face.
That's called respect.
Mmm.
Who is the lucky brunette?
Last name Beeswax,
first name None-of-ya.
Oh, my third wife was biracial.
Oh!
Stop it.
I am just trying to
keep you out of trouble.
What if the next girl saw these?
Well, then she would
know it was hers.
Jeff,
you're sleeping with a woman
you already slept with?
Can't I be the friend
in the group
whose trademark
is his well-defined boundaries?
Like Privacy Smurf,
Discreet Bear, or --
Confidentiality Spice?
But if you like her,
why would you wanna
keep her a secret?
Don't you want us to meet her?
We have an agreement
to keep it low-key.
That's ridiculous.
Obviously, it's a guy.
You're wrong, Pierce.
It's two guys.
Sometimes,
I do wish you were dead.
Thank you.
♪ "At Least It Was Here" - The 88 ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
Hey, what's up, man?
Boo!
Hey, what's up, J-Dog?
Arf arf arf arf!
Yeah!
Hey, what's up, man?
What's up?
Sorry I'm late.
Uh, and step into place.
Six, seven, eight, and reach.
Two, three, four, pose.
Reach back,
and arm!
Professor Slater,
quick question.
You know the answer, Mr. Winger.
I don't date students.
Even if you are no longer
in my statistics class.
I'm actually kind of seeing
someone right now.
Thank you very much.
Really?
How's that going?
Fine, for now.
She's smart and pretty.
But sometimes, I feel like
she's just waiting for me
to stop talking
and take off my pants.
She is.
I've never been someone's
dirty little secret.
I've never had a dirty little secret.
It's so unprofessional.
But the sneaking does make
the sex 38% hotter.
Wow, you do like statistics,
don't you?
- Hey, midterms and whatever.
- Chalk.
Professor Slater, there's
that transcript you wanted.
Jeff, I didn't expect
to see you here.
Hopefully, I'm not...
interrupting.
You know, we laugh,
but the fact is, student-teacher
relationships do happen.
And they are a magnet
for lawsuits,
so we do stay vigilant.
In fact,
physically attractive
students and faculty
are actually placed
on a watch list.
And are ranked
by their potential
to incite fraternization.
You rank people
by how hot they are?
You got it,
number two.
Dean Pelton.
Yes, Professor Seven...
Uh, Slater?
I'll return this tomorrow.
Okay, then.
You guys be extra careful now.
Two people of your rankings
in this small a room,
with this type of lighting,
and --
his upper body, and what
her heels and hemline
are doing to enhance
what were already
quite a few favours
from God,
it's all the more important
to keep it tasteful.
I think he might have ruined...
It's dead.
Two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
Arm, head,
and pose!
I can't wait for the recital.
You were all wonderful.
Especially you, Troy.
Thank you, Madame LeClair.
And if any of you mention
my dancing outside of class,
I will break off your legs
and use them to smash
in your friends' cars.
Oh!
Huh!
- Oh, my God...
- Oh, my God.... !
Troy,
since when have you taken
Modern Dance?
Since last semester.
Coach told me it would help
with my coordination.
And I fell in love with it --
in a very straight way.
I know it's tempting
to sneak a peek,
but I'm gonna need for you
to keep your eyes
up here.
I should have never dismissed
you as a shallow jock.
Then again, we haven't
really spent much time together.
That's because
you don't play football
or, have fun.
I have fun tap-dancing.
I started last semester too.
It was always something
that I wanted to do, but it was --
too embarrassing,
so I never told anyone.
Same here.
Britta,
nobody can know about this.
Troy, who are we kidding?
Look at how much time and energy
we're putting
into hiding something
that we're passionate about.
We are leading a double life.
I am spending a lot of money
on breakaway clothing.
We should look at this
as an opportunity to come clean.
Are you saying
we tell the group?
Together?
We could invite them
to the dance recital on Friday.
Man, I don't know.
Let me think about it.
Okay, let's do this.
Ahem!
Sorry.
Mr. Winger.
Would you come to my office?
We never finished
our intercourse.
I have study group right now.
And -- nobody uses
"intercourse"
to mean anything other than sex.
Hmm.
Look, this is a wall of windows.
My study group's behind it.
I know.
Look, as soon as we touch,
the blinds will open,
and six annoying
but lovable misfits
will be staring at us.
Come on,
what are the odds?
Fine.
Now, was that so bad?
Hey!
Could you open the back door?
You all remember
Michelle Slater,
my professor from last semester?
As most of you
may have realized by now,
she's the woman
I've been seeing lately.
Why are they looking at me
like I'm a zoo animal?
Well, Jeff acts as
sort of the Dad of the group.
So, emotionally,
this is kind of like being told
that you're our new Mom.
But, you know
it's nothing like that,
right?
Absolutely.
Do you cook macaroni?
I have.
Macaroni's my favourite.
The important thing is,
we all understand
Professor Slater and I
need this
to be our little secret.
Everyone understand that?
Sure, sure.
So good, the pepperjack.
See? All good.
Well, thank you, everyone.
I appreciate it.
- I should get going.
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
- Ooh.
Bye.
Well, Jeff,
you've taken a big step
in knocking down the barriers
between students and teachers.
It's like Rosa Parks.
I don't think it's like that.
No, it's just like that.
I feel if you need to explain it,
it's not just like that.
Is your heart gonna be okay
with this?
I will try to find the tools
to survive.
Okay.
Hey, everybody,
speaking of secrets,
Troy and I have something
that we would like to announce.
No, no.
There is a dance recital
on Friday,
and I would be honoured
if you guys would attend.
Because since last semester,
I --
have been taking a tap class.
That's...
... funny.
Well, I don't know
how funny it is...
Come on, we're not
making fun of you,
but, obviously,
you kept it a secret
because you saw the irony, too.
Irony?
Well, you're not a typically
vulnerable or feminine person.
And the act of dancing
is considered
both vulnerable and feminine.
Mm-hmm.
I disagree.
What about Fred Astaire?
What about Baryshnikov?
Yeah, I guess...
There are exceptions
to the rule.
But even when Jerry Rice went
on Dancing With the Stars...
Jerry Rice?
Oh, I liked him.
Troy,
what's your secret?
Um...
M... My secret --
is that...
I... knew Britta's secret.
Yeah.
I saw her in her dance outfit
and she looked ridiculous.
So I helped her protect
her shame.
You know,
I'm just glad she's out now.
Bravo, Britta.
Thanks.
Mr. Winger, there you are.
Just got word
of your relationship
with Professor Slater.
I'd like to see both of you,
in my office, in half an hour.
What the -- ?
None of you left the room.
How is that even possible?
Well, for one thing,
it's all over Twitter.
Britta in a tutu.
Can you imagine?
Hey!
What the hell?
I thought we were
supposed to come out to
the group together.
Yeah.
I changed my mind.
Well, they're gonna find out
that you dance at the recital.
I'm not gonna be in the recital.
I'm dropping the class.
Oh, my God.
How can you do this to me?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Hey, you don't get to talk
to me like that.
You are not Shirley.
And Shirley's not my Mom.
Britta, it's not like
we were in the same boat.
Girls are supposed to dance.
That's why God gave them parts
that jiggle.
But -- I'd be going
from starting quarterback
to a guy
that twirls around in tights.
I've got way more to lose
getting up on that stage
because I'm a man.
Well, guess what.
A real man doesn't bail
on his friends,
or on himself.
You're a dancer, Troy.
It's who you are.
Not anymore.
Excuse me.
Whoa.
Come on!
Upset about Jeff?
No, I am upset about...
... something
I can't talk about.
We can talk about anything.
Politics, medicine,
Jeff.
Okay, uh, did you hear
that the Shroud of Turin
is actually...?
Here's the thing about Jeff.
Wow.
Chasing after you made him
a better person
because you always call him
on his stuff.
All this time,
you've been warming him up
and stirring in sweetener,
and --
making him just right.
And sure, you weren't ready
to take a sip yet.
But that didn't mean
you wanted somebody to --
snatch him off the counter
and guzzle him down, right in front of you.
Shirley, I did not warm Jeff up.
Nobody ever will.
Do you think Professor Slater
is getting flowers right now?
Do you think they
are gonna go to the movies
and hold hands?
Visit her parents?
No.
The only thing keeping
them going
was the thrill of the secrecy.
And now that it is out,
it is over.
Believe me.
Can...
Can I just ask,
as a divorced, black housewife,
what part of being
a single, white slacker
makes you people so jaded?
Ooh.
"You people"?
What do you mean, "you people"?
I cannot believe
I got to say that.
It's the little things,
isn't it?
Okay, well, now that
your secret is out there,
I'm just gonna talk you through
this teacher-student relationship form,
and then --
we can get you two
on your very attractive way.
We haven't even admitted
to being a couple.
And, in fact,
this is all based on hearsay.
Worse than hearsay.
Pierce's Twitter account,
in which he says he's 47,
and teaches a women's
only Pilates class.
Jeff, it's okay.
It's out.
And you know what?
It doesn't bother me.
I'm happy.
Sweet.
First question.
How long have you been doing it?
Oh, not "it."
I mean, this,
dating.
A few weeks.
Mm-hm.
And...
how long have you been doing it?
We don't have to answer that.
Oh, it's...
Hmm?
Now,
this is just hypothetical.
Might you ever consider spending
the night with a third person?
That's not on there.
Uh...
Wow, it's on there.
Just exploring your options,
obviously.
No agenda.
I'll put TBD.
Would you describe yourself
as boyfriend and girlfriend?
- Yes.
- Eh...
What?
Oh, boy.
It's -- semantics,
really, isn't it?
We've slept together every night
for the last three weeks.
How would you describe me?
The best friend ever.
Oh.
Well, uh...
I guess I've had
the wrong idea about us.
Wh -- you know what?
This is good. I --
I'd be better off dating,
um, an adult.
See you around.
Michelle.
Mmm.
Rawr... !
I'll get the breakup form.
I got freaked out
by that boyfriend label.
I'm...
afraid of commitment.
How original.
Well ,the biggest truths
aren't original.
Truth... is ketchup,
it's Jim Belushi.
Its job isn't to blow our minds,
it's to be within reach.
So the truth is,
I get claustrophobic
when things get official.
You're acting like
I'm a Venus flytrap.
I didn't want or need more
than what we were doing.
Let's get back to it.
Should I get the door?
I can't now because
you went to the friend place.
That's -- you getting official,
not me.
Because unless there's something
I need to know
about the lunch lady, or that
blond in your Spanish class
with the infinite supply
of leather jackets,
somewhere between our ninth
and eleventh slumber party,
statistically speaking,
most people
would call us more than pals.
Yeah, but soon as you say it,
it can get complicated
and messy.
How?
Because when you say it,
later on,
you might have to unsay it.
Whoopee flipping ding, Winger.
It happens 50 million times a day.
It's the Jim Belushi
of sexual commitments.
It barely means anything,
and it grows on
what's there over time.
Wow, that guy is really taking
a pounding
in this conversation.
I'll see you around, Jeff.
I really liked
what we were doing.
And... if the ratio of work
to pleasure
can really stay
at that same level,
I don't care what it's called,
I'll do it.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Oh. That's a big crowd
out there.
Abed's really good
at inviting people.
We're all here to support you.
Jeff even brought
his girlfriend.
Oh, she's his girlfriend now?
Can't wait till he hears
about it.
Oh, he knows.
They even had to file
paperwork with the Dean.
It's pretty serious.
Our little Jeff's growing up.
Oh!
Break a leg, Britta.
I have no idea
how someone could do
what you're about to do.
I brought Goobers.
Anybody want a Goober?
Get them while they're goobie.
Yeah!
Showtime.
Well, this is
already ridiculous.
Shh.
"Tea for Two"?
There...
there's five people.
Shh!
Good Lord.
Is she a water pot
or a tea kettle?
Shh!
Any of you think the flowers
are dying from the tea?
Shh!
Everyone can hear you.
Shh shh shh shh shh!
Britta.
Water it.
What's going on?
So embarrassing.
Ungh!
Oh...!
Plot twist.
Easy, girl.
There we go.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Play something modern.
What are you doing here?
Being a friend and a man.
Holy... !
Yikes.
Ah!
It's okay.
Culturally, it's unacceptable,
but it's theatrical dynamite.
Whoo!
Bravo!
Whoo.
Yeah, alright.
Greendale.
Arf!
Arf, arf, arf!
Greendale!
Hi, guys. That was really cool.
I wish I knew how to tap dance.
Oh. Thanks, Abed.
It takes a lot of hard work,
but you could always take a class.
Hmm, pass.
Hey, Troy,
thank you.
No, thank you.
I mean, you looked so pathetic,
you made going up there
the most masculine option.
Mmm.
Troy.
Oh.
What you did up there
really took guts.
I'm impressed.
Thanks, Pierce.
Yeah.
And such a creative way
to tell the world you're gay.
Good job up there.
Thank you.
Where's your date?
Didn't she wanna get
my autograph?
Oh, she's getting a
permission slip from the Dean
to allow us
to drive home together.
Heard you guys are official now.
Yeah, I guess.
You actually
had a big part in that.
I mean, if I can handle
having a --
girl for a friend,
who's to say I'm not ready
for a girlfriend?
Makes perfect sense.
Break a leg.
Flowers.
Yeah.
Uh, is that... ?
That's what people do, right?
I was gonna --
throw 'em up
on stage,
but I thought
they might catch fire.
No, this is... This is good.
You can...
You can hand them to me.
Thank you.
- See you Monday.
- Bye.
♪ "Merry Happy" - Kate Nash ♪
♪ Dancing at discos ♪
♪ Eating cheese on toast ♪
♪ Yeah, you make me merry ♪
♪ Make me very, very happy ♪
♪ But you obviously ♪
♪ You didn't want
to stick around ♪
♪ So I learnt from you ♪
♪ Do, do, do...
da, do, do ♪
♪ Do, da, do, do... ♪
♪ Da, do, do...
do, da, do, do... ♪
♪ Da, do... ♪
Good night, everybody!
Five letters, Broadway musical.
Annie.
Uh, six letters, to puncture.
Pierce.
Um, a water filter
that starts with B.
Brita.
Okay.
Here's a tough one, though.
Um, Helen, of --
Troy.
- Oh, damn, you're good.
- Thank you.
I never even heard
of that last one.
Alright, uh, one of the two
brother actors, Bridges,
four letters.
Hmm.
I know...
Bridges.
I don't know.
Come on, guys,
can't you see the pattern there?
Can you see it?
It's Beau,
Beau Bridges.
These are all things
you can see on TV.
Except for "pierce,"
That's a misdirect.
Oh.
I love misdirects.
I love The Big Lebowski.